dailyfeed.co.uk 2019-07-13

# Privacy Policy • Daily Feed

**Privacy Policy**

**Daily Feed Ltd  **trading as  **DailyFeed.co.uk** , a company registered in England and Wales under company number 09728689 whose registered address is at 76 Quay Street, Manchester, hereinafter referred to as ‘ **DailyFeed** ’ or ‘ **We** ’ have created this privacy statement (‘ **Statement** ’) in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of the details that You provide to us when using [http://www.DailyFeed.co.uk](http://www.timetobreak.com/) (the ‘ **Site** ’) and the DailyFeed Services. When You use the Site and the DailyFeed Services, You are consenting to the practices set forth in this Statement.

We know that Your privacy is very important to You which makes it very important to us. We aim to be as clear as possible in this Statement in respect of Your Personal Data. This Statement applies inter alia to Your Personal Data that We collect about You when You use the Site, how and when it is used, how We protect it and who has access to it.

**1.**

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE STATEMENT**

This Statement governs Your use of the DailyFeed Services, including any dispute concerning privacy. By using the DailyFeed Services, You accept this Statement in full. You should read the Statement carefully and ensure that You understand its effect before proceeding to use the Site and the DailyFeed Services. We reserve the right to modify this Statement at any time without notice by posting the changes on this page. Your continued use of any portion of the Site following the posting of the updated Statement will constitute Your acceptance of the changes.

**2.**

**WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED & HOW?**

**A.**

**PERSONAL DATA**

**2.1**

The Site asks You to provide various types of Personal Data to enhance the quality of the DailyFeed Services We can provide to You and the more accurate the information You provide, the better We are able to respond to Your requirements! As part of the process of using the Site and the DailyFeed Services, We may collect the following types of Personal Data about You (as applicable):

•Your first name, last name, email and password (upon Sign-Up as a DailyFeed Member on the Site);

•Your gender, house number, date of birth, postcode and photo (upon further entering a Prize Draw and accruing Entries in Your Entries Bank by undertaking certain DailyFeed Member Actions);

•Your visits to the Site and the DailyFeed Content that You download;

•Your UGC that You may upload or submit to the Site;

•information about Your computer (including Your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and Site navigation);

•any other information that You choose to send to us, including any request for further DailyFeed Services, general correspondence, reports of a problem with the Site or the DailyFeed Services.

•information relating to any Prize Draws entered in to by You on the Site and any Prize Draws which You have been a Winner; and,

**B.**

**OTHER DATA**

**2.2**

Other  _de-personalised_  data which does not record Personal Data as such, rather information such as the date of Your visit to the Site, the path taken, the browser used, the IP address etc is used primarily to aid the technical administration of the Site, to better understand how the Site is functioning for DailyFeed Members and to draw conclusions upon demographic information.

**3.**

**HOW IS THE INFORMATION USED?**

**3.1**

You hereby expressly consent to Your Personal Data being passed on to third party companies or service providers for the sole purpose of fulfilling the DailyFeed Services only (including making improvements to the DailyFeed Services) and not for the purposes of those third parties making marketing communications to You, unless You have expressly consented to this being undertaken by a third party (“ **DailyFeed Partners** ”).  **DailyFeed Partners include our DailyFeed Retailers who provide the Prizes so although You are under no obligation to provide such Personal Data to us, however, if You choose not to, some of the DailyFeed Services may not be available to You**.

**3.2**

You acknowledge that Your Personal Data may be used by DailyFeed to contact a DailyFeed Member by post, phone or by electronic mail when necessary in connection with Your use of the Site and the DailyFeed Services including Your DailyFeed Membership.

**3.3**

From time to time, DailyFeed may contact You by electronic mail (or by telephone) by way of sending You various confirmations, notifications, feedback requests or any other newsletter or information or offers regarding upcoming DailyFeed promotions, services or customer surveys. If You change Your mind, You can opt out of receiving some but not all of this as some are required as a necessary part of delivering the DailyFeed Program and for operating the DailyFeed Membership in order to continue to receive access to the DailyFeed Services. You cannot opt out of receiving the DailyFeed Membership Verification Email, the DailyFeed Membership Email or the Winner Alert.

**3.4**

You can opt out of receiving direct marketing communications from DailyFeed as described below.

**3.5**

Your Personal Data is used solely by DailyFeed (and DailyFeed Partners to the extent necessary to fulfil the DailyFeed obligations to You and the DailyFeed Retailer obligations to You where applicable) for the sole purpose of enabling DailyFeed to act as a service provider to You and is not shared with any person or company without Your express consent.

**3.6**

Any Personal Data that is held with DailyFeed shall be retained in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and related Data Protection Legislation and/ or our retention and destruction policy culminating in its permanent deletion.

**3.7**

If Personal Data has been passed to third parties with Your consent, You may need to contact them separately if You change Your mind in relation to their use of Your Personal Data.

**OPTING OUT:**  If You do not wish to be contacted by DailyFeed in respect of future marketing communications, We will give You the opportunity to unsubscribe to the receipt of such communications in every electronic mail communication that We send to You. Alternatively and additionally, You can contact DailyFeed by sending an email to this [email address](mailto:alex@gosocialmarketing.co.uk) with “UNSUBSCRIBE REQUEST” in the subject line or send Your request by post to DailyFeed at the contact address below.

**4.**

**WHO HAS ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA?**

**4.1**

To minimise the risk of unauthorised access to Your Personal Data, We use some of Your Personal Data to authenticate You when using the Site and the DailyFeed Services.

**4.2**

For our daily operations, We may use the DailyFeed Services of third parties to provide some of our business and operational functions. Consequently, some of the DailyFeed Services are provided by DailyFeed Partners and We need to disclose Your information to them to provide You with the DailyFeed Services.

**4.3**

**Disclosure of Your Personal Data in Compliance with Laws  **

You should be aware that We may release Your Personal Data when We believe it is necessary to comply with laws or regulations, to assist law enforcement, to enforce the terms under which You transact or communicate with or via DailyFeed, or to protect the rights, property or safety of DailyFeed, DailyFeed Members or third parties.

**4.4**

**Transfer of Your Personal Data outside of the EEA  **

From time to time, We may transfer Your Personal Data to a related company, agent or contractor in order to improve our DailyFeed Services or to assist our security, credit risk or fraud protection activities. Such companies may be located outside of the EEA and You consent to the transfer of Your Personal Data to such companies for the purposes set out here in accordance with this Statement and as permitted by the Data Protection Legislation from time to time.

**4.5**

**Transfer of Personal Data in the Event of the Sale of DailyFeed.co.uk or its Assets**

In the event that DailyFeed.co.uk is sold or transfers some of its assets to another party, Your Personal Data could be one of the transferred assets. If Your Personal Data is transferred, its use will remain subject to this Statement. Your Personal Data will be passed on to a successor in interest in the event of a liquidation or administration of DailyFeed.

**4.6**

**Other Sites and their Privacy Policies and Cookie Policies**

The Site may contain links to other websites. DailyFeed is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites or for the privacy policies, cookie policies and practices of other third parties, so You should be careful to read and understand those website policies independently.

**5.**

**HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA & FOR HOW LONG?**

**5.1**

The privacy and protection of Your Personal Data is important to us. In addition, any DailyFeed Member statistics that We may provide to prospective DailyFeed Partners regarding Your usage of the DailyFeed Services are provided in the aggregate only and do not include any individually identifiable data.

**5.2**

You acknowledge that email messages sent over the internet are not encrypted and are not secure. Despite efforts to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any Personal Data You transmit to us, via, to, or from our Site. You accept that DailyFeed cannot be held liable for any breaches of confidentiality that may occur as a result of the use of email. If there is any sensitive or confidential Personal Data which You do not wish to communicate by email, please contact DailyFeed by telephone or post to arrange an alternative method of communication.  **You transmit all such Personal Data at Your own risk**.

**5.3**

How long We keep Your Personal Data collected through our Site depends on the context in which You provide it and the purpose for which We use it. We will only retain it for as long as is necessary for such purposes. We may send You direct marketing communications for as long as You do not unsubscribe from receiving the same from DailyFeed. In the event that You choose to close Your DailyFeed Member Account, all Your Personal Data will be deleted from the Site.

**5.4**

**Telephone calls** : If You call any of the service telephone numbers quoted on this Site, We may record Your call. These recordings are used for training and quality control to ensure that We continuously monitor and improve our service standards.

**6.**

**COOKIES** :

For information about cookies and how they are used on this Site, please visit our Cookie Policy.

**7.**

**COMPLAINTS OR QUERIES**

DailyFeed tries to meet the highest standards when collecting and using Personal Data. For this reason, We take any complaints We receive about this very seriously. We encourage You to bring it to our attention if You think that our collection or use of Personal Data is unfair, misleading or inappropriate. We would also welcome any suggestions for improving our procedures. This Statement does not provide exhaustive detail of all aspects of DailyFeed’s collection and use of Personal Data. However, We are happy to provide any additional information or explanation needed. Any requests for this should be sent to the address below. If You are not happy with the way in which Your Personal Data is being handled by DailyFeed, You can complain to the Information Commissioner whose details can be found at: <http://www.ico.org.uk/>[ ](http://www.ico.org.uk/)

**8.**

**ACCESS TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA**

DailyFeed tries to be as open as it can be in terms of giving people access to their Personal Data. Individuals can find out if We hold any Personal Data by making a ‘subject access request’ under the Data Protection Act 1998. If We do hold Personal Data about You, We will let You have a copy of that Personal Data. To make a request to DailyFeed for any Personal Data that We may hold, You need to put the request in writing addressing it to the address provided below. They may be an administrative charge applied in accordance with the applicable legislation.

**9.**

**HOW TO CONTACT US**

Requests for information about our Statement or a ‘subject access request’ can be emailed to this [email address](mailto:alex@gosocialmarketing.co.uk) or by writing to:

Daily Feed Ltd  **trading as**  DailyFeed.co.uk (Internal Compliance Department)

76 Quay Street

Manchester

M34PR

**10.**

**CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT**

We keep our Statement under regular review. This Statement was last updated on 25 July 2014.
